Where The Passion ends... the story of Paul begins.
Saint Paul is a adventure, drama, tv movie film directed by Roger Young.
A biblical epic from the Book of Acts and Paul's epistles covering his
conversion from Saul of Tarsus to his ministry to the Gentiles.
Paulus, played by Johannes Brandrup.
Ruben, played by Thomas Lockyer.
Dina, played by Barbora Bobuľová.
Simon Petrus, played by Ennio Fantastichini.
Johannes, played by Giorgio Pasotti.
Gamaliel, played by Franco Nero.
Paul the Apostle (Italian: San Paolo, German: Die Bibel – Paulus), also known as Saint Paul,
is a 2000 television film written by Gareth Jones and directed by Roger Young.
The film is based on real life events of  Christian apostle and Saint Paul.
The film explores themes of christianity, apostle,
bible, religious film, 1st century.
The tone is emotional.